Kolya Harutyunyan

Frontend Developer

Respected Frontend Developer with about 3 years of experience in collaborating with creative and development teams on the execution of ideas and projects. Key skills include: ● Promoting and communicating new ideas ● Creating process improvements ● Instituting new technologies ● Writing maintainable cross-browser code ● Estimating time and costs for projects ● Ensuring code is scalable and responsive



- haryan.geko@gmail.com
- Yerevan, Armenia
- in linkedin.com/in/kolya-harutyunyan-3a11a320b
- S live:.cid.80f67e47f57f1f6f

- +37498741604
- kolyaharutyunyan.github.io/my-portfolio/
- witter.com/Kolya80264360
- github.com/KolyaHarutyunyan

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Solicy

12/2022 - 02/2023

Yerevan, Armenia

Frontend Web Developer ITHire

05/2020 - 11/2021

Yerevan, Armenia

Achievements/Tasks

- Translate designs to front-end code, estimate project time and costs, determine developer requirements and specifications, and work with cross-functional team to define and develop product roadmaps.
- Notable accomplishment:

 Increased scalability,
 maintainability, and responsiveness of cross-browser code.

Frontend Web Developer Eachbase

11/2021 - 11/2022

Yerevan, Armenia

Achievements/Tasks

- Updated and streamlined existing code to improve site performance for entire company. Notable Accomplishments:
 - Utilized cutting-edge JavaScript and HTML 5 techniques, frameworks, and libraries. ■ Wrote support documentation and provided training to internal and external users.

EDUCATION

Faculty of Regulation of Economy and International Economic Relations
ASUE (Armenian State University of Economics)

09/2015 - 05/2020

Yerevan, Armenia

SKILLS



LANGUAGES

Armenian

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Russian

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

